Contact

christianlashay@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/christian-iwobi-fnp-bc-0a150845 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Familiar with EHR systems
Documentation
HIPAA

Certifications

Science and Applications of Cosmetic Lasers in Medical Aesthetics

Science and Application of Botox Cosmetic Dermal Fillers for Soft

Certificate of Training for Cutera Yag 1064 for Hair Removal, Vascular Treatment and Genesis

FNP-BC

ACLS

Christian Iwobi, FNP-BC

Family Nurse Practitioner

Plano, Texas

Summary

Family Nurse Practitioner seeks Women's health care/Infertility practice opportunities that will advance comprehensive health care education, focus on culturally appropriate and holistic patient-centered care, and provide a constant learning environment.

Goals are to gain more experience in women's health, medical aesthetics, and to learn medical spanish.

Experience

Pacific Reproductive Services
Family Nurse Practitioner
July 2013 - March 2018 (4 years 9 months)

- Provide initial patient consultation, infertility evaluation and treatment.
- Obtain detailed medical history, review medical records and perform appropriate physical examination.
- Perform thorough infertility evaluation to include ultrasonography, routine gynecological exams, and interpretation of laboratory values.
- Collaborate with physician as needed in developing and implementing treatment plan appropriate to individual patient.
- Perform ultrasonography, Intra-Uterine Insemination, and monitoring of cycles.
- Evaluated women with Polycystic Ovarian Syndrome, Chronic Pelvic pain, Endometriosis and other various gynecological disorders; implemented appropriate therapy, or refer to Medical Director for treatment.
- Supervise clinical staff, implement organizational systems, oversee personnel scheduling and issues.
- Provide patient counseling and education on pertinent health issues.
- Respond positively to patient questions and concerns.

Planned Parenthood Los Angeles Mid level Clinician May 2012 - June 2014 (2 years 2 months) Canoga Park

- Male and Female genital exams, physical exams, wet mounts, STD screenings, family planning/birth control services.
- Patient teaching and education on STD/HIV prevention, preventing pregnancy, and birth control options.
- Insertion of Nexplanon and IUD's to prevent pregnancy.

One Staff Medical
Registered Nurse
June 2011 - March 2012 (10 months)

Travel nurse position in ICU at Ridgecrest Regional Hospital.

Patient and family educator, healthcare provider, emotional supporter utilizing case management resources to patients across the socio-economic spectrum. Met high quality standards while providing patient care on various in-patient and out-patient healthcare units.

West Hills Hospital and Medical Center Registered Nurse July 2009 - April 2011 (1 year 10 months)

Managed patient care through a high performing team of licensed and unlicensed personnel. Collaborated with physicians and support staff to provide quality care.

Provided education, compassion, and specialized nursing care to patients on Cardiac Observation Unit.

Monitored telemetry patients and prepped patients for cardiac procedures.

MinuteClinic Nurse Practitioner 2010 - 2011 (1 year)

Ensured each patient received comprehensive medical care while working independently as a single point of contact in a retail based health care setting that employs the medical model for patient care.

Provided education, instruction, and support as a preceptor to NP students while assisting in training and skills validation of new hires and continuing employees, resource and support person to colleagues.

Educated patients on health related issues using out of the box thinking for holistic care with 96% of patients stating an ease of understanding of the presented medical information.

Demonstrated expertise in acute care management and treatment procedures.

Emerald Health Services, RN Network, Westways Staffing

Travel Nurse January 2008 - January 2009 (1 year 1 month)

Worked as travel nurse on telemetry/step down unit in Bakersfield, CA and Northridge, CA.

Managed patient care through a high performing team of licensed and unlicensed personnel. Collaborated with physicians and support staff to provide quality care.

Provided education, compassion, and specialized nursing care to patients in my care.

Coordinated patient care via supervision and delegation of licensed and unlicensed personnel.

Huntsville Hospital Registered Nurse May 2003 - January 2008 (4 years 9 months)

Education

University of Alabama in Huntsville MSN, Nursing · (2004 - 2006)

University of Alabama in Huntsville BSN, Nursing · (2001 - 2003)